Bangladesh on rest, latest updates, good evening.
Tensions are escalating on the Indo-Bangaladesh border as Dhaka takes a hard line against
New Delhi.
On Thursday, the Bangladesh Foreign Ministry's summon India's High Commissioner, flagging
serious security concerns for Indian diplomatic missions in the country.
Officials warned that recent attacks on Indian nationals and the looting of Indian consular
properties have created an unacceptable environment for diplomats.
The move follows a wave of protests that erupted after a Hindu shopkeeper was killed in the
Chittagon Hill tracks, igniting communal fury across Bangladesh.
Demonstrators have set up barricades outside the Indian High Commission in Dhaka.